dwr.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy & Security

Design Within Reach is committed to respecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. We will not sell or disclose any information that identifies you to a third party if requested. In addition, when you place an order with Design Within Reach your personal information and credit card information are safe. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

##### What information does Design Within Reach collect?

When making a purchase through our Site, we collect your name, billing address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card information, in order to process your order. Therefore when you visit our Site to place subsequent orders we can save you time by providing your previous account information for you. If you request a catalog, we collect your name, mailing address and e-mail address. Once we have collected an email address, we send our weekly email newsletter informing you of news and our special product offers. You are welcome to visit our Site without providing any of this information; however, we are unable to process an order or send a catalog or newsletter without the requested information.

We use cookies, which is a feature of your browser used to assign identification to your computer. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer – but not you – to our servers every time you visit our site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user, but may be correlated with identity information in our log files. You can decline cookies through your browser preference options, but you may not be able to use some of our services properly as a result, such as the option to save your user name and password.

We also collect the IP address of visitors to our Site and collect aggregate information about the use of our Site. All information described in this section entitled "What information does Design Within Reach collect?" constitutes "Data" for purposes of this Privacy Policy.

Design Within Reach may collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the Website through the use of trusted third party partners. These partners may also combine your email information with other information they have access to such as mailing address so that Design Within Reach may serve relevant marketing offers to you via email and direct mail. If you do not want Design Within Reach to collect information about you, please contact us to opt out.

Top

##### How does Design Within Reach use the data it collects?

We use the Data collected from you primarily to process and fulfill your orders, to notify you of the status of your orders, to send our weekly e-mail newsletter, or to send you targeted marketing information, special product offers, catalogs or other information that we believe might interest you. In every such e-mail, we will have instructions on how to unsubscribe and avoid receiving any future e-mails from us. Please see our Opt Out Policy section below.

We also may combine information you have provided to us in communications offline – such as information related to your catalog subscription and orders – with the Data you have given us online, to provide a more customized experience for you when you visit our Site.

Top

##### Communications from Design Within Reach to you

We may contact you by e-mail to respond to customer service questions you have submitted, or to address a problem affecting your use of the Site, or to send you a confirmation message upon completion of the account registration process.

Top

As part of our commitment to your privacy, Design Within Reach adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise to American Consumers." We periodically make information, including aggregated information, available to selected third parties, including but not limited to those who share information for direct marketing purposes. You may instruct us not to share information with third parties by calling us at [800.944.2233](tel:800-944-2233), emailing us at [service@dwr.com](mailto:service@dwr.com) or writing to us at: 

Design Within Reach  
711 Canal St., 3rd floor  
Stamford CT 06902

Design Within Reach does not make your email address or phone number available to third parties.

We may disclose your Data to a third party if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process requires it, to protect the rights or property of Design Within Reach or others, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

Notwithstanding any other provision, we may also engage a third party partner for the purpose of identifying users and delivering to them interest-based content and advertisements. We may share information about you with our partners such as a non-human-readable form of your email or other identifier to ensure the security of your information. Our partners also may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, device ID, and information about your browser or operating system; may combine our personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources; and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. To opt-out of BouncePilot’s services, please go to http://BouncePilot.com/opt-out/. To opt out of LiveRamp’s services, please go to http://www.liveramp.com/opt_out. To opt-out of third party cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices. To opt-out of the use of your mobile device ID for targeted advertising, please see http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices.

Top

##### How Is Your Information Protected?

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All orders are transmitted over secure Internet connections using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology. All of your personal information including your credit card information and sign-in password are stored in encrypted format at all times. This Website, and more importantly all user information, is further protected by a multi-layer firewall based security system.

Top

##### Opt Out Policy

If you’d prefer not to receive our catalog, or if you’re receiving unwanted extra copies, then please [unsubscribe here.](https://www.dwr.com/catalog-opt-out.html?lang=en_US) If you would prefer not to receive our newsletter, you may use the remove functionality located at the bottom of each newsletter, or send an e-mail to [remove@dwr.com](mailto:remove@dwr.com) with 'unsubscribe' in the subject line. Please be sure to e-mail us from the address that you want removed. Furthermore, if you would like to specify that you would not like to share your information for rental, sales or exchanges, please email us at [service@dwr.com](mailto:service@dwr.com).

You can also call us at [800.944.2233](tel:800-944-2233) if you would like to be removed from any of our lists.

You may always choose not to provide us with any of the information we request; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific product or service.

Top

##### Correcting and updating your information

Users of our Site are able to modify their account information, such as shipping and billing addresses, each time they place an order with us.

Top

##### Links to other sites

Design Within Reach contains links to other sites not affiliated with Design Within Reach. These sites have their own policies and practices with respect to online privacy, and Design Within Reach cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of these unaffiliated web sites.

Top

##### Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about Design Within Reach's information collection practices, please contact us at [service@dwr.com](mailto:service@dwr.com).

Top
